Guide to the Fales Portrait/Subject Collection ca. 1800 - 1998 MSS.034
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I
  - Talfourd, Sir Thomas Noon, Undated (Box 5, Folder 622)
  - Talleyrand de Périgord, Charles Maurice, Undated (Box 5, Folder 623)
  - Talleyrand, Prince of Benevento Tarkington, Undated (Box 5, Folder 624)
  - Taylor, Bayard, Undated (Box 5, Folder 625)
  - Taylor, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 626)
  - Taylor, Tom, Undated (Box 5, Folder 627)
  - Tempski, Armine von, Undated (Box 5, Folder 628)
  - Tenison, Thomas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 629)
  - Tennyson, Alfred Lord, Undated (Box 5, Folder 630)
  - Terry, Marion, Undated (Box 5, Folder 631)
  - Thomassin, S., Undated (Box 5, Folder 632)
  - Thomson, James, Undated (Box 5, Folder 633)
  - Thomas, Dylan, Undated (Box 5, Folder 634)
  - Thompson, Sylvia, Undated (Box 5, Folder 635)
  - Thoreau, Henry David, Undated (Box 5, Folder 636)
  - Thorhill, Sir James, Undated (Box 5, Folder 637)
  - Thoyras, Rapin de, Undated (Box 5, Folder 638)
  - Thurston, Ernest Temple, Undated (Box 5, Folder 639)
  - Tickell, Thomas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 640)
  - Tilson, Henry, Undated (Box 5, Folder 641)
  - Timotheus, Undated (Box 5, Folder 642)
  - Tintoretto, Jacopo Robusti, Undated (Box 5, Folder 643)
  - Titian, Vecellio, Undated (Box 5, Folder 644)
  - Tombleson, Undated (Box 5, Folder 645)
  - Tomlinson, Major Henry, Undated (Box 5, Folder 646)
  - Tompson, Richard, Undated (Box 5, Folder 647)
  - Tonson, Jacob, Undated (Box 5, Folder 648)
  - Tooke, John Horne, Undated (Box 5, Folder 649)
  - Torrentius, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 650)
  - Towneley, Charles, Undated (Box 5, Folder 651)
  - See Oversize, Folder 2 Trade Winds galleys (by Christopher Morley), Undated (Box 5, Folder 651-A)
  - Trask, Katrina, Undated (Box 5, Folder 652)
  - Traven, B., Undated (Box 5, Folder 653)
  - Trevelyan, George Macaulay, Undated (Box 5, Folder 654)
  - Trevelyan, George Otto, Sir, Undated (Box 5, Folder 655)
  - Trevelyan, Hilda, Undated (Box 5, Folder 656)
  - Trinx, John W., Undated (Box 5, Folder 657)
  - Trollope, Anthony, Undated (Box 5, Folder 658)
  - Trollope, Frances, Undated (Box 5, Folder 659)
  - Troubetskoy, Prince Pierre Troubetzkoy, Amélie (Rives), Undated (Box 5, Folder 660)
  - Truman, Mrs. Daniel Tully, Jim, Undated (Box 5, Folder 661)
  - Tupper, Martin Farquhar, Undated (Box 5, Folder 662)
  - Tyrwhitt, Thomas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 663)
  - Tyler, Anne, Undated (Box 5, Folder 664)
  - Union Volunteer Refreshment Saloon Updike, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 665)
  - Vachell, Horace Annesley, Undated (Box 5, Folder 666)
  - Vanderbank, Peter, Undated (Box 5, Folder 667)
  - Van de Velde, Willem Van de Velde, William (son), Undated (Box 5, Folder 668)
  - Van Dyck, Sir Anthony, Undated (Box 5, Folder 669)
  - Van Dyck, Antonio Van Dyke, Henry Van Loon, Hendrik, Undated (Box 5, Folder 670)
  - Vansomer, Paul, Undated (Box 5, Folder 671)
  - Vernet, Claude Joseph, Undated (Box 5, Folder 672)
  - Verrio, Antonio, Undated (Box 5, Folder 673)
  - "Victoria Regina", Undated (Box 5, Folder 674)
  - Victoria, Queen of Great Britain, Undated (Box 5, Folder 675)
  - Victorian Fashions, Undated (Box 5, Folder 676)
  - Views Villiers, Charles Pelham Viva Voltaire Vonnegut, Kurt, Undated (Box 5, Folder 677)
  - Wagner, John Wain, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 678)
  - Waithman, Robert Wakoski, Diane, Undated (Box 5, Folder 679)
  - Walcott, Derek Walker, Alice Wall, Evans, Undated (Box 5, Folder 680)
  - Walker, David Walker, Mildred Walker, Robert, Undated (Box 5, Folder 681)
  - Waln, Nora Walpole, Horace, Undated (Box 5, Folder 682)
  - Walpole, Sir Hugh, Undated (Box 5, Folder 683)
  - Walton, Edna Lou Walton, Izaak, Undated (Box 5, Folder 684)
  - Ward, Elizabeth Stuart (Phelps), Undated (Box 5, Folder 685)
  - Ward, Mary A. Ward, Christopher, Undated (Box 5, Folder 686)
  - Ward, Samuel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 687)
  - Wardle, Gwyllyn Lloyd, Undated (Box 5, Folder 688)
  - Warren, Robert Penn Warner, Sylvia Townsend, Undated (Box 5, Folder 689)
  - Warren, Samuel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 690)
  - Warren, Sir John Borlase, Bart. Wasserman, Jacob, Undated (Box 5, Folder 691)
  - Watson, Edward Watson, Elkanah Watson, Kate (Southey), Undated (Box 5, Folder 692)
  - Watt, James Watts-Dunton, Theodore, Undated (Box 5, Folder 693)
  - Waugh, Evelyn, Undated (Box 5, Folder 694)
  - Webster, Daniel Weidman, Jerome, Undated (Box 5, Folder 695)
  - Welldon, Fay Wellesley, Richard Colley Wellesley, Marquis of, Undated (Box 5, Folder 696)
  - Wellington, Arthur Wellesley, 1st Duke of, Undated (Box 5, Folder 697)
  - Wellington, Richard, Duke of, Undated (Box 5, Folder 698)
  - Wells, Herbert George Welty, Eudora, Undated (Box 5, Folder 699)
  - Werfel, Franz West, Benjamin West, Herbert West, Rebecca Weston, Christine, Undated (Box 5, Folder 700)
  - Westall, Richard Westcott, Edward Noyes Weyman, Stanley, Undated (Box 5, Folder 701)
  - Wharton, Edith, Undated (Box 5, Folder 702)
  - Wheatley, Henry Benjamin, Undated (Box 5, Folder 703)
  - Whistler, James A. McNeill, Undated (Box 5, Folder 704)
  - [Empty], Undated (Box 5, Folder 705)
  - Whitbread, Lady Elizabeth (Grey) Wilbur, Richard, Undated (Box 5, Folder 706)
  - Whitbread, Samuel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 707)
  - White, E.B. White, Robert, Undated (Box 5, Folder 708)
  - White, Steward, Undated (Box 5, Folder 709)
  - White, William Allen, Undated (Box 5, Folder 710)
  - Whittier, John Greenleaf, Undated (Box 5, Folder 711)
  - Whiting, Richard, Undated (Box 5, Folder 712)
  - Whittock, N., Undated (Box 5, Folder 713)
  - Whitworth, Charles, Earl of, Undated (Box 5, Folder 714)
  - Wiggin, Kate Douglas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 715)
  - Wilberforce, William, Undated (Box 5, Folder 716)
  - Wilde, Oscar, Undated (Box 5, Folder 717)
  - Wild, Jonathan Wilde, Percival, Undated (Box 5, Folder 718)
  - Wilder, Robert Wilder, Thornton, Undated (Box 5, Folder 719)
  - Wilkes, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 720)
  - Wilkes, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 721)
  - Wilkins, William, Undated (Box 5, Folder 722)
  - Willett, M., Undated (Box 5, Folder 722-A)
  - William, Earl of Chatham, Undated (Box 5, Folder 723)
  - Williams, Ben Ames Williams, Emlyn Williams, William Carlos, Undated (Box 5, Folder 724)
  - William, Frederick, King of Russia, Undated (Box 5, Folder 725)
  - William, Henry IV, Undated (Box 5, Folder 726)
  - William III, King of Great Britain, Undated (Box 5, Folder 727)
  - Williams, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 728)
  - Williams, Jonathan Williams, Tennessee Williamson, Henry Williamson, Thames Willingham, Calder, Undated (Box 5, Folder 729)
  - Willis, Nathaniel Parker, Undated (Box 5, Folder 730)
  - Wilson, A.N. Wilson, John ("Christopher North"), Undated (Box 5, Folder 731)
  - Wilson, Richard, Undated (Box 5, Folder 732)
  - Wilson, Sir Robert T., Undated (Box 5, Folder 733)
  - Wilton, Marie, Undated (Box 5, Folder 734)
  - Winstanley, Hamlet, Undated (Box 5, Folder 735)
  - Winthrop, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 736)
  - Wissing, William, Undated (Box 5, Folder 737)
  - Wolcot, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 738)
  - Wolfe, General James, Undated (Box 5, Folder 739)
  - Wolfe, Thomas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 740)
  - Wood, Ellen (Mrs. Henry), Undated (Box 5, Folder 741)
  - Wood, Sir Matthew, Bart., Undated (Box 5, Folder 742)
  - Woodberry, George Edward, Undated (Box 5, Folder 743)
  - Woolf, Virginia, Undated (Box 5, Folder 744)
  - Wordsworth, William, Undated (Box 5, Folder 745)
  - Worlidge, Thomas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 746)
  - Wren, Sir Christopher, Undated (Box 5, Folder 747)
  - Wright, Harold Bell, Undated (Box 5, Folder 748)
  - Wright, Thomas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 749)
  - Wylie, Eleanor Wyndham, William, Undated (Box 5, Folder 750)
  - Yashinsky, Daniel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 751)
  - Yates, Edmund Hodgson, Undated (Box 5, Folder 752)
  - Yeats, William Butler Yezierska, Anzia, Undated (Box 5, Folder 753)
  - Yonge, Charlotte M., Undated (Box 5, Folder 754)
  - Zangwill, Israel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 755)
  - Zuccaro, Federigo, Undated (Box 5, Folder 756)
  - Zukofsky, Louis Zweig, Paul, Undated (Box 5, Folder 757)
- Oversize
  - Alfieri, Vittorio Bobst, Elmer Holmes Byron, George Gordon Cooper, James Fenimore Goethe, Johann Wolfgang Irving, Washington Moore, Thomas Schiller, Friedrich Scott, Sir Walter, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Boswell, James, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Coleridge, S.T. Pitt, William Shelley, Percy B. Southey, Robert Wordsworth, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Disraeli, Benjamin D'Orsay Johnson, Samuel Parr, Samuel Porson Priestly, JosephTrade Winds gallery (written by Christopher Morley; published 1940), Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Florence, Mrs. Florence, William Jermyn Forrest, Edwin; Murdoch, James E.; Raymond, John T., Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    All images are photogravure prints of the actors in costume
  - Fox, Charles James Pitt, William Wilkes, John, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Kaprow, Allan, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 6a)
  - 1797 Plan of the City of New York (1853 re-print) 1807 Plan of the City of New York, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Scott, Sir Walter, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Trade Winds gallery (written by Christopher Morley; published 1940), Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)